This is an e-ink display that
automatically updates throughout the day
with anything that you want. [music]
There's no touchscreen, there's no
notifications, and most importantly,
there's no subscriptions. As someone
who's been using this for over a year,
it's an insane workstation upgrade. I've
set it up so that it switches between
custom views like newspaper headlines
once a day, my latest YouTube stats,
[music] and even my daily habit streak.
They have thousands of plugins that you
can just plug and play, or you can even
write code your own. I also have the
smaller version of this, which I use to
display my calendar constantly [music]
on my desk, so never miss a meeting
again.